Lisa Groen

+31 (0)6 4549 - 1808 lisatgroen@hotmail.com Amsterdam, Noord-Holland, the Netherlands

https://lisaag.github.io/ https://www.linkedin.com/in/lisa-groen-bb298816b/

Master student Game and Media Technology at Utrecht University. Mostly experienced within the field of game development and VR/AR development. Open to learning all kinds of skills within the field of software engineering.

SKILLS

Programming Languages	C#C++Python	 HTML, CSS, Javascript
Tools/Libraries	UnityUnreal Engine	Blender, MayaOpenCV, Tensorflow

EDUCATION

02/2023 - Present	Game and Media Technology (Master's)
-------------------	--------------------------------------

Utrecht University - Utrecht

- Computer Vision (Machine Learning, Tensorflow, OpenCV)
- Software Optimization (GPGPU, OpenCL, SIMD), Ray tracing

11/2021 - 12/2022 **Japanese Language**

Academy of Language Arts – Tokyo, Iidabashi

- Focused on learning Japanese Language for daily and business use
- Conversational and written Japanese (speaking, reading, writing)

09/2016 - 08/2020 HBO-ICT - Game Development (Bachelor's)

Amsterdam University of Applied Sciences – Amsterdam

- Focused on learning a broad set of different skills within the field of ICT, focussed on Game Development.
- Object Oriented languages (C#, C++, Java)
- Game Engines (Unity, Unreal Engine, Game Maker)
- Web development, Embedded systems and IoT development, Game development and VR/AR development.

EXPERIENCE

09/2024 - 11/2024 **Teaching Assistant**, Utrecht University – Utrecht

- Teaching Assistant of course Multimedia Retrieval
- Providing practical assignment support

https://u-pad.nl

- Board meetings, organizing events
- Communication with members and externals

01/2021 - 10/2021 **AR software engineer**, Miracle Mile – Tokyo, Chiyoda-ku https://miraclemile-inc.com/ • Mobile AR development (Apple, Android) • AR development for head mounted hardware (Hololens 2) IoT development using Arduino and M5Stack combined with Microsoft's Hololens 2 • Realtime online cross-platform application development Microsoft Azure **Game programming intern**, Shinyuden - Tokyo, Chiyoda-ku 03/2020 - 08/2020 https://www.shinyuden.com/ Creating a procedurally generated 3D world environment inside Unity Engine • Game concepting and design • Game programming (C#, Unity Engine) Shader programming 09/2019 - 01/2020 **VR software engineer intern**, Therapieland - Amsterdam https://therapieland.nl/ • VR software development (HTC Vive) Procedural mesh generation • Game concepting and design 3D modeling 01/2018 - 07/2018 **Software engineer intern**, Digital Society School – Amsterdam https://digitalsocietyschool.org/ Secondary research Concept creation, prototyping and peer testing • Static website development (HTML, CSS)

Languages

Dutch (native)

English (fluent)

• Embedded systems (Arduino, C)

• Japanese (JLPT N2)